<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Sawwheet</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Sawwheet</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 08:11:00 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Who I Strive to Be</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/who-i-strive-to-be/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 08:11:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/who-i-strive-to-be/</guid>
      
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I cannot pinpoint exactly who I am, for that would be taking a snapshot of a moment that immediately passes. My desires, actions, and thoughts are ever changing and the best I can do is use whatever sense of will I have to direct myself in the direction I see fit. This direction is built by reflection on my own experience, observation of the world around me, and learning from those that I admire.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lake of the Past</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/20250601t124910--lake-of-the-past__journal/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jun 2025 12:49:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/20250601t124910--lake-of-the-past__journal/</guid>
      
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A lot of times in life you seem to have no idea what you are looking
for. There is a yearning for something more, something to fill you up,
but you don&amp;rsquo;t know what it is. That is not how I feel. I know exactly
what I am looking for, and I know exactly where to find it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The problem with what I am looking for, is that it is on the other
side of a lake. This lake is slowly expanding and as a result, what I
seek is becoming further away. I jump in and start swimming, but the
freezing water only adds to the pain.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Equilibrium of Nature</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/20250531t130911--equilibrium-of-nature__journal/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 May 2025 13:09:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/20250531t130911--equilibrium-of-nature__journal/</guid>
      
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I am discovering that nature has a calming affect on me. The pain and longing of the breakup are
still present, but the feelings aren&amp;rsquo;t as intense. The calm environment, and the exertion of the
hike seem to allow for a little more balance to creep in. I wish she, or the version of her I have
in my head, was here with me, but I am able to find some peace on my own.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Limbo</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/20250519t073601--limbo__poem/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 07:36:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/20250519t073601--limbo__poem/</guid>
      
      <description>&lt;p&gt;For her, there is love and respect;&lt;br&gt;
For me, there is sadness and regret.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The hope holds strong,&lt;br&gt;
but it cannot be trusted.&lt;br&gt;
The pain is proglonged,&lt;br&gt;
as long as it survives.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Will there be another?&lt;br&gt;
Will it meet the same fate?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am stuck in limbo;&lt;br&gt;
I am stuck in my head.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Path</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/20250515t191453--the-path__journal/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 19:14:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/20250515t191453--the-path__journal/</guid>
      
      <description>&lt;p&gt;All is good; The path is well lit. There are steep inclines and rough terrain. But not to worry, the
path paves the way.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In a single moment, it goes dark. Another moment goes by, and the path is gone. The incline grows
steeper, and the terrain rougher.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The traveler sees a single light in the far off distance, and hopes the path will return. Another
path has been paved, but it does not lead to the desired destination. The traveler is left with a
choice.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zion - Ragnar Relay</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/zion-ragnar-relay/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 16:47:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/zion-ragnar-relay/</guid>
      
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This past weekend I ran a &lt;code&gt;Ragnar Relay Race&lt;/code&gt; near Zion national park. Given the proximity, I of
course took the opportunity to visit Zion as well. A little foreshadowing: the majority of the hikes,
including Angel&amp;rsquo;s Landing and The Narrows, are shuttle access only.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I went into the park on two different days. The first day was the day I drove in, so it wasn&amp;rsquo;t until
mid afternoon. I met up with my brother and we made our way down to the visitors center. This is
also where you park, and take the shuttle as mentioned earlier. The parking lot was PACKED, luckily
we were both able to find a spot, and ended up doing one of the 2 hikes that did not require a
shuttle.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eljira Announcement</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/eljira-announcement/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 08:37:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/eljira-announcement/</guid>
      
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/sawwheet/eljira&#34;&gt;Eljira&lt;/a&gt; is an Emacs interface into Jira.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I had three main motiviations in creating this project:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I hate Jira, and none of the existing interfaces fit my needs (mainly custom field related)
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;For something so central to my work, it is super inefficient to navigate.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I wanted to dig my teeth into lisp&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I want the trolls to tear apart an open source project of mine&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Unfortunately I cannot give too much of a visual demo, becaus the only Jira instance I have access
to is my employers. Redacting info, or creating a new personal Jira instance is work I don&amp;rsquo;t want to
do. With that said, here is a general overview of the project:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>In and Out</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/in-and-out/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 13:29:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/in-and-out/</guid>
      
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In represents focus. Attention is directed towards the task at hand; Your mind is at capacity with
context of the work.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Out represents wandering. Taking a step back to observe the whole, and letting consciousness flow.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The meeting point of in and out represents moderation; It represents harmony. When you over indulge in
the out, you become out of touch. You forget that human life, all life, requires work. While lost in
the out, you risk becoming trapped in the depths of the meaningless void. Too much time spent in,
and appreciation disappears. Deep within the in are the little things; These little things latch on,
but they do not matter.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Miss Jane</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/miss-jane/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2025 16:38:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/miss-jane/</guid>
      
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I have a question;&lt;br&gt;
to which there is no answer.&lt;br&gt;
Perhaps upon reflection,&lt;br&gt;
I will find direction.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Beyond the door,&lt;br&gt;
the embrace of clarity.&lt;br&gt;
The teacher is fair,&lt;br&gt;
and she will listen.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Outside is rain,&lt;br&gt;
a cloud of shame.&lt;br&gt;
I go back the way I came.&lt;br&gt;
Until next time Miss Jane.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What I Feel</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/what-i-feel/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2025 08:11:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/what-i-feel/</guid>
      
      <description>&lt;p&gt;What I feel is confusion. It is sadness, and a longing. There is disappoinment, and there is hope.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Confusion arises when the day is good, and the moment is sad. Longing sinks in when she breathes
indifference. Disappointment overwhelms when efforts are not reciprocated. Yet there is hope,
in the form of adventure.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I want to run away. I want to seek meaning and connection in new places. The remedy seems to sit in
the heart of adventure, needing only courage. It is a temporary measure, of that I am aware. The
human condition does not care.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
