<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Sawwheet</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Sawwheet</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 08:37:00 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Eljira Announcement</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/eljira-announcement/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 08:37:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/eljira-announcement/</guid>
      
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/sawwheet/eljira&#34;&gt;Eljira&lt;/a&gt; is an Emacs interface into Jira.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I had three main motiviations in creating this project:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I hate Jira, and none of the existing interfaces fit my needs (mainly custom field related)
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;For something so central to my work, it is super inefficient to navigate.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I wanted to dig my teeth into lisp&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I want the trolls to tear apart an open source project of mine&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Unfortunately I cannot give too much of a visual demo, becaus the only Jira instance I have access
to is my employers. Redacting info, or creating a new personal Jira instance is work I don&amp;rsquo;t want to
do. With that said, here is a general overview of the project:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>In and Out</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/in-and-out/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 13:29:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/in-and-out/</guid>
      
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In represents focus. Attention is directed towards the task at hand; Your mind is at capacity with
context of the work.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Out represents wandering. Taking a step back to observe the whole, and letting consciousness flow.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The meeting point of in and out represents moderation; It represents harmony. When you over indulge in
the out, you become out of touch. You forget that human life, all life, requires work. While lost in
the out, you risk becoming trapped in the depths of the meaningless void. Too much time spent in,
and appreciation disappears. Deep within the in are the little things; These little things latch on,
but they do not matter.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Miss Jane</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/miss-jane/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2025 16:38:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/miss-jane/</guid>
      
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I have a question;&lt;br&gt;
to which there is no answer.&lt;br&gt;
Perhaps upon reflection,&lt;br&gt;
I will find direction.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Beyond the door,&lt;br&gt;
the embrace of clarity.&lt;br&gt;
The teacher is fair,&lt;br&gt;
and she will listen.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Outside is rain,&lt;br&gt;
a cloud of shame.&lt;br&gt;
I go back the way I came.&lt;br&gt;
Until next time Miss Jane.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What I Feel</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/what-i-feel/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2025 08:11:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/what-i-feel/</guid>
      
      <description>&lt;p&gt;What I feel is confusion. It is sadness, and a longing. There is disappoinment, and there is hope.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Confusion arises when the day is good, and the moment is sad. Longing sinks in when she breathes
indifference. Disappointment overwhelms when efforts are not reciprocated. Yet there is hope,
in the form of adventure.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I want to run away. I want to seek meaning and connection in new places. The remedy seems to sit in
the heart of adventure, needing only courage. It is a temporary measure, of that I am aware. The
human condition does not care.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
