<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Journal on Sawwheet</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/journal/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Journal on Sawwheet</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Jun 2025 12:49:00 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/journal/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Lake of the Past</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/20250601t124910--lake-of-the-past__journal/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jun 2025 12:49:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/20250601t124910--lake-of-the-past__journal/</guid>
      
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A lot of times in life you seem to have no idea what you are looking
for. There is a yearning for something more, something to fill you up,
but you don&amp;rsquo;t know what it is. That is not how I feel. I know exactly
what I am looking for, and I know exactly where to find it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The problem with what I am looking for, is that it is on the other
side of a lake. This lake is slowly expanding and as a result, what I
seek is becoming further away. I jump in and start swimming, but the
freezing water only adds to the pain.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Equilibrium of Nature</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/20250531t130911--equilibrium-of-nature__journal/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 May 2025 13:09:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/20250531t130911--equilibrium-of-nature__journal/</guid>
      
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I am discovering that nature has a calming affect on me. The pain and longing of the breakup are
still present, but the feelings aren&amp;rsquo;t as intense. The calm environment, and the exertion of the
hike seem to allow for a little more balance to creep in. I wish she, or the version of her I have
in my head, was here with me, but I am able to find some peace on my own.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>In and Out</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/in-and-out/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 13:29:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/in-and-out/</guid>
      
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In represents focus. Attention is directed towards the task at hand; Your mind is at capacity with
context of the work.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Out represents wandering. Taking a step back to observe the whole, and letting consciousness flow.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The meeting point of in and out represents moderation; It represents harmony. When you over indulge in
the out, you become out of touch. You forget that human life, all life, requires work. While lost in
the out, you risk becoming trapped in the depths of the meaningless void. Too much time spent in,
and appreciation disappears. Deep within the in are the little things; These little things latch on,
but they do not matter.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
